binarium.com 2017-06-06

# Binarium

The Companys primary interest lies in the safeguarding of its Clients privacy, by ensuring that all personal data which is obtained from its Clients, including all the data that is obtained by Binarium Ltd when a Client visits the Companys websites. Information collected by Binarium Ltd is handled, retained and processed only by means that are in accordance with mandatory legal requirements and only to the extent it is strictly necessary for the achievement of the purposes set out herein. By opening a trading account with Binarium, you as a client, are giving your consent to the collection and use of your personal information, in the manner described in the rules below.

#### The collection of personal information

Binarium collects the necessary information required to open a clients real or demo trading account, perform transactions and safeguard the clients assets and privacy and to provide clients with the services they require. In this respect, the Company gathers information from clients and may, in certain circumstances, gather information from banks and/or credit agencies, and/or clearing agencies and/or other sources which will help the Company to construct the clients profile based on their requirements and preferences in order to provide its services effectively.

The data Binarium collects includes information required to communicate with and identify its clients, such as the data given by the client at the time of registration on the companys website. It is under clients responsibility to provide real, accurate and up to date personal information and not misrepresent himself to be another individual or legal entity. Any changes in the Client's identifying details shall be notified to the Company immediately.

#### Use of personal data

Personal information is collected by Binarium for the following uses:

  * The confirmation of Clients identity;
  * To prevent Money Laundering;
  * Maintaining the clients personal profile and managing his account
  * For the analysis of the data, to provide the customer with the most suitable products and services;
  * To inform about promotions and additional products;
  * Keeping accurate information within companys database;

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone and is stored on your device's hard drive for tracking site usage. Many websites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows. A Client may choose to configure their browser to reject cookies by modifying their browser settings or preferences. Please note that by deleting or disabling cookie files, a client may not be able to access certain components or use certain Website features.

The Company uses cookies to secure clients trading activities and to enhance the performance of the Binarium website. Cookies used by the Company do not contain personal information or other sensitive information.

#### Protection of personal data

Any personal information provided by the client to the Company will be treated as confidential and shared only within the Company and its affiliates and will not be disclosed to any third party except under any regulatory or legal proceedings. In case such disclosure is required to be made by law or any regulatory authority, it will be made on a need-to-know basis, unless otherwise instructed by the regulatory authority. Under such circumstances, the Company shall expressly inform the third party regarding the confidential nature of the information.

Personal customer data may be disclosed for processing to any member of the group of companies and their employees, who have a need to know such information; to any third party that provides services of the company on its behalf in order to allow or enable the company to provide customer with trading services; to any third party, which provides the company with the services related to handling the website; to any auditors, contractual or other advisors of the auditors who conduct audits of any company's business processes, and to any potential buyers or investors of the company. All third parties with which the company shares the personal information, will be obliged by the Company to protect such data in accordance with all relevant legislative acts, and in a form similar to the one the company uses for protecting such information. The company will not distribute personal information to those third parties, which are considered as unable to provide a proper level of protection of such data.

#### Security

Binarium takes the issue of security very seriously and takes all possible measures to ensure the safety of your confidential information. All transactions on Binarium website are safe, as the company uses a server certificate, also known as a digital certificate, which guarantees the identity of the company, as well as the advanced SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption of the transmitted data; The Company does not save or store any credit or debit card information. To prevent any unauthorized access to clients credit card information, it is transferred to the company in shortened form through a secure server.

#### Passwords

Upon registration to Binarium.com, Client will be asked to choose a username and password to be used on each future login and for the performance of Transactions and use of the Company's Services. In order to protect Clients' privacy and operation with Binarium, sharing registration details (including without limitation, username and password) by Client with other persons or business entities is strictly prohibited. The Company shall not be held responsible for any damage or loss caused to Client due to improper use (including prohibited and unprotected use) or storage of such username and password, including any such use made by a third party, and whether or not known to or authorized by Client. Any use of Binarium.com with the Client's username and password is Client's sole responsibility. The Company shall not be held responsible for any such use, including for validation that Client is actually operating in his/her Account. Client is obliged to forthwith notify the Company's client service of any suspicion for unauthorized use of the Account.

#### Links to other websites/services

We have no control over other websites, services or applications that provide information, advertisements, over banners or links from within the Site or Service. These third party websites, services or applications may use their own cookies or place other files on your hard disk. Subject to the third partys own privacy policy, personal data may be collected. We recommend that you read any third party privacy policies listed on their websites, services or applications before using them.

#### The Protection of Minors

Binarium website is open to the public, however it is not aimed at individuals under 18 years of age. If the Company becomes aware that a minor attempted to or has submitted personal information, the company may reject this information and delete it from its server without any preliminary notification.

#### Changes in the rules

The Company may update the rules from time to time. Any changes in the rules will be published on the website.
